A Finding Aid to the Wilbur H. Burnham Studios Records, circa 1904-1991, in the Archives of American Art AAA.wilbhbur
Archives of American Art
- Project Files, 1916-1980s; Series 6; 10.6 Linear feet Boxes 2-12, 42
  184. Holyoke, Our Lady Perpetual Help
  185. Mechanicsville, NY, balcony window, Frye
  186. Mechanicsville, NY, aisle and clerestory, Frye
  187. Cleveland, OH, First Baptist
  188. Wakefield, Universalist Church
  189. Gloucester, L. Buswell
  190. Transparency, Monkey, Bush
  191. Winthrop, C. L. Covington
  192. Natick, Morse Institute
  193. Fall River, St. Mark's 4/18/40
  194. Montgomery, AL, Ch. Ascension
  195. New York, Cath. St. John Divine, 5 apse clerestory 450 sq. ft.
  196. Sample, Exhibition, Hotel Penn., New York
  197. Clifton, O. Ch. Annunciation
  198. Sample for Mr. Hoyle
  199. New York, Christ Ch., Mosaics
  200. Lynn, First Universalist
  201. Repair, Quincy, Atlantic Methodist
  202. New Haven, CO, Evergreen Cemetery Chapel
  203. Litchfield, CO, St. Michael's Church aslo #210
  204. Chicago, IL, First Presbyterian Church
  205. Lexington, Hancock Congregational
  206. Fitchburg, St. Bernard's Convent Chapel
  207. Brookline, Temple Israel
  208. East Boston-two windows-quarry
  209. West Roxbury, Austrian Hungarian Society
  210. Litchfield, CO., St. Michael's door lights see #203
  211. Valhalla, Long Island, Gate of Heaven Cemetery
  212. Albany, St. Andrews, aisle, St. Paul
  213. Cambridge, book case
  214. Westfield, St. Mary's lower church
  215. Cleveland, OH, First Baptist, Dr. Phillips'single lancet
  216. Milford, Trinity Church, rose, Miss Brent
  217. Toledo Museum, Music transparency
  218. Boston, Old South church, Children's Chapel
  219. Palmer, St. Thomas Church
  220. West Roxbury, Church of Holy Name
  221. Watertown, CO, Christ Church-2 lancet window
  222. Newton, Finkelstein, quarry
  223. Boston, Emmanuel Church
  224. Albany, NY, St. Andrew's, five windows
  225. Chestnut Hill, Ch. Redeemer, choir window
  226. Hampton, NH, 1st Congregational Church
  227. Boston, Ch. Disciples, Frye
  228. Cambridge, First Unitarian
  229. St. Agatha, Maine, Ch. St. Agatha
  230. Portland, Maine, Mr. Graham
  231. Transparency repair-Veritas
  232. Bronx, NY, St. Helena
  233. Washington Cathedral, Peter, Paul, Joan of Arc
  234. Worcester, Chestnut St. Congregational
  235. Washington Cathedral, Peter Paul, Color scheme
  236. Newton, Mr. Porder (2 small king and queen)
  237. Bronx, NY, Carmelite Monastery
  238. Dorchester, St. Matthews
  239. Salisbury, MD, St. Peter's (4 lancets)
  240. Dover, NH, St. Thomas Episcopal Church, inscription
  241. Roxbury, Jewish Cemetery, inscriptions
  242. Repair, Boston, Mt. Vernon
  243. Peoria, IL, St. Mary's Cath., Good Shepherd panel
  244. Albany, NY, St. Andrews: Sts. Luke, Stephen, George
  245. Watertown, CO, Christ Church, Bread of Life
  246. Peoria, IL, St. Mary's Cathedral, St. Thomas More, ceiling, see #178
  247. Lynn, Miss McCarthy, Dining Room
  248. West Haven, CO, Christ Church
  249. New Britain, CO, Ch. Holy Cross
  250. Roxbury, Temple Mishkan Tefila
  251. Cambridge, Harvard-Epworth, Methodist repair
  252. Northampton, Mr. Putnam
  253. West Roxbury, Ch. of the Holy Name repair
  254. Albany, St. Andrew's Church
  255. Punxsutawney, Pa, Cosmos and Damian
  256. Whitinsville, Trinity Ch.
  257. New York, Holy Ghost Chapel, Stearns and Stanton
  258. Clinton, First Congregational Church
  259. Boston, repair
  260. Turners Falls, Congregational
  261. Wash. D. C., Cath. Peter Paul, Apse window, Resurrection
  262. Baltic, CO, Academy of the Holy Family
  263. Boston, Hotel Lenox repair
  264. Albany, St. Andrew's Ch., Joan of Arc, Augustine, Seabury, Bishop Doan, Cranmer, Wycliffe, St. Francis Assisi
  265. Repair, Boston, lantern
  266. Westfield, St. Mary's Ch., 22 aisle, 3 sanc., 13 clerestory
  267. Austin, TX, Presbyterian Theological Seminary rose
  268. Winter Park, FL, Rollins College
  269. Winter Park, FL, All Saints
  270. New York, Cath. St. John Divine, baptistry
  271. Bridgeport, CO, Methodist Ch.
  272. Repair, Brookline, All Saints Ch.
  273. Lantern slides made 1940 (entire year)
  274. Adams, First Congregational Ch.
  275. Atlanta, GA, Mrs. McBurney
  276. Repair, Maynard
  277. Repair, Boston, Mr. Sargent
  278. Sample, grisaille #164
  279. Groton, Baptist Ch.
  280. Repair, Newton
  281. Chelsea, St. Rose's Ch.
  282. Albany, NY, St. Paul's Ch.
  283. Worcester, All Saints
  284. Westfield, St. Mary's, Stations of the Cross
  285. Peoria, IL, St. Mary's Cath., lightening windows
  286. Bellaire, OH, Trinity Episcopal
  287. Lantern slide, Joan of Arc
  288. Newton, Temple Emmanuel
  289. Westfield, St. Mary's Baptistry
  290. Holyoke, Our Lady of Perpetual Help, Rose Dollard and Joan of Arc windows
  291. Springfield, Holy Family (repair aisle in shop)
  292. West Roxbury, Holy Name, gates
  293. Roslindale, Ch. Our Savior
  294. Westfield, St. Mary's Gallery Window
  295. Westfield, St. Mary's 3 tympanum
  296. Westfield, St. Mary's 2 small angel (5 entrance)
  297. Transparencies, Christmas angels
  298. Brookline, Mr. Green
  299. Springfield, Holy Family, clerestory, sanctuary
  300. Exhibition, Boston, Bornstein
  301. Cambridge, Mt. Auburn
  302. Repair, Winter Park, FL, Rollins College
  303. Winchester, Congregational
  304. Gales Ferry
  305. Exhibition, Boston, St. Paul's Cath.
  306. Boston, Station WMEX
  307. Pittsfield, St. Mary Morning Star, Rose
  308. Springfield, Holy Family, 10 door lights
  309. Springfield, Holy Family, altar aisle tracery
  310. Pittsfield, St. Mary Morning Star, 32 clerestory
  311. Boston, Ch. Covenant
  312. Holyoke, Sisters of Providence
  313. Spotswood, N. J., St. Peter's Episcopal
  314. Repair, Brookline, Wm. J. Barry
  315. Attleboro, St. John's Ch., quarry
  316. Pittsfield, St. Mary Morning Star, 10 nave
  317. Pittsfield, St. Mary Morning Star, 12 boys and chapel sacistry
  318. Pittsfield, St. Mary Morning Star, 7 amb. clerestory
  319. Pittsfield, St. Mary Morning Star, 6 chapel
  320. Pittsfield, St. Mary Morning Star, 4 nave
  321. Watertown, Mr. Porter
  322. Pittsfield, St. Mary Morning Star, confessionals, etc.
  323. Newton, Mr. Leo Mayer
  324. Repair, Attleboro, St. John's Ch.
  325. Westfield, St. Mary's, door lights
  326. Westrield, St. Mary's, plate
  327. Lancaster, Immaculate Conception Ch.
  328. Albany, NY, Madison Ave. Presbyterian
  329. Boston, Bachrach
  330. Cambridge, Episcopal Theological
  331. Ipswich, Ascension Memorial
  332. Wakefield, Mr. B., repair
  333. Everett, Universalist Ch.
  334. Roxbury, Mr. Libby
  335. Albany, St. Andrew's Resurrection
  336. Fall River, St. Mark's 2 transept, Christ blessing children and Boy Christ
  337. Brookline, estimate, Honsberg
  338. Repair, panels
  339. Albany, NY, St. Andrew's clerestory
  340. Colorado Springs, Grace Episcopal Ch.
  341. Portland, ME, Mercy Hospital
  342. Wash. D. C., Cath. Peter Paul, Center Apse, Christ in Glory
  343. Fall River, St. Mark's, Resurrection, Tomb
  344. Pittsburgh, Mellon Chapel
  345. Fredericksburg, MD, St. George's, large window
  346. Springfield, St. Michael's Cath.
  347. Boston, U. S. Quartermaster Depot
  348. N. Adams, St. John' Ch.
  349. New Bedford, St. Andrew's Ch.
  350. Dorchester, Baptist Temple
  351. Brookline, Mr. Macmillan
  352. Braintree, Emmanuel Ch.
  353. Holyoke, Ch. Holy Rosary
  354. Providence, R. I., Mr. Long
  355. Fredericksburg, 3 door lights
  356. Dorchester, Baptist Temple
  357. Boston, Repair
  358. Boston, Mrs. Turner
  359. Worcester, Odd Fellows Home
  360. Boston, Mr. Collens
  361. Boston, Mrs. Hamilburg
  362. Greenwood, Most Blessed Sacrament
  363. Brookline, St. Lawrence Ch.
  364. Boston, Kingsley School
  365. Brookline repair
  366. Concord, Trinity Ch., rose
  367. Roxbury, Ch. St Theresa, rose
  368. Boston, Touraine
  369. Manton, R. I., St. Peter's
  370. Wash. D. C., Rock Creek, St. Paul's Ch. three nave
  371. Pittsfield, St. Mary's M. S. 29 doors
  372. Fredericksburg, St. George's Ch. repair
  373. Roslindale, Ch. Our Saviour
  374. Boston, Hotel Touraine
  375. Concord, Trinity Ch. lancets
  376. Pawtucket, R. I., Trinity Church, door light
  377. Fredericksburg, St. George's Ch. repair
  378. Transparency, Choate
  379. Wash. D. C., Red Cross
  380. Portland, C. H. Farley Co.
  381. Wash. D. C., Rock Creek, St. Paul's Ch. one tower
  382. Jamaica, N. Y., Bishop Molloy Retreat House
  383. Norfolk, Va. David Adams Memorial Chapel: 1 over side; 2 vestibule windows; 9 aisle; 2 side windows; 6 door lights; 1 over west; 6 narthex
  384. Fredericksburg, St. George's Ch. repair
  385. Repair, Boston, Swan
  386. Repair, Boston, Presbyterian
  387. Norfolk, Va. Our Lady of Victory Chapel, rose
  388. New Bedford, St. James Ch.
  389. Pawtucket, R. I., Trinity Ch., clerestory
  390. Sample of #344, Mellon
  391. New Bedford, Grace Ch.
  392. Cleveland, OH, Euclid Avenue, Joan of Arc, Wycliff, St. Francis Assisi
  393. Elyria, Ohio, St. Andrew's, Presentation in the Temple, Flight into Egypt
  394. Sample, #180
  395. Boston, repair, I. J. Fox
  396. Worcester, Exhibition, general
  397. Transparency, Jr. ship oblong 9 x 11
  398. Transparency, Ernest's little round ship
  399. Transparency, Rubiyat, glass upturned
  400. Transparency, Rubaiyat IV - 58
  401. Transparency, Rubaiyat, Bird of Paradise
  402. Transparency, Erica's Madonna and Child
  403. Transparency, Tahitian girl, Wallis
  404. Transparency, ship, painted black round
  405. Transparency, art and literature
  406. Transparency, Egyptian charioteer
  407. Worcester, Sacred Heart Ch.
  408. Albany, St. Andrew's, 2 entrance, Lochner
  409. Columbus, OH, Trinity Ch., designs only
  410. Columbus, OH, Trinity Ch., 2 on south side
  411. Fall River, St. Mark's, Gethsemane
  412. Brunswick, Me., St. Paul's Ch.
  413. Repair, Wakefield, Fussy
  414. Repair, Peoria
  415. Norfolk, Our Lady of Victory Chapel, 7 aisle
  416. Norfolk, David Adams Memorial Chapel, one chancel window
  418. Norfolk, David Adams Memorial Chapel, 1 circle, 1 window over balcony
  419. Transparency, bunny
  420. Transparency, Christ Child and lamb
  421. Transparency, Puss in Boots
  422. Transparency, Rooster
  423. Roslindale, Ch. Our Saviour, Transept Window Fisk Memorial
  424. Wash. D. C., Rock Creek, St. Paul's Ch. repair
  425. Repair, Linden
  426. Repair, Dedham
  427. Repair, Boston
  428. Transparency, St. Luke
  429. Repair, Mr. Barber
  430. Cleveland, OH, First Baptist, St. Mark
  431. Exhibition, Modern Art
  432. Wash. D. C., Rock Creek, St. Paul's Ch. two nave windows
  433. Albany, St. Paul's, 4 chapel
  434. Transparency pig
  435. Winchester, Ch. Epiphany, 3-lancet tower
  436. Repair, Boston
  437. Sutton, Congregational
  438. Northampton, St. John's
  439. Dedham, Ch. Good Shepherd, 2 lancet
  440. Repair, Leech
  441. Albany, NY, St. Andrew's, 2 chapel
  442. Pawtucket, RI, Trinity Ch., St. Michael's
  443. Brookline, Torf Memorial Chapel
  444. Brookline, St. Paul's Ch.
  445. Camp Lejeune, N. C., chancel
  446. Norfolk, VA, U. S. Naval Air Station
  447. Boston, Bethlehem Steel
  448. Worcester, St. John's Ch.
  449. Providence, St. Martin's
  450. Roxbury, St. Theresa's
  451. Holyoke, Sacred Heart
  452. Norfolk, Va. - Our Lady of Victory Chapel, 3 entrance
  453. Auburn, N. Y., 2nd Presbyterian
  454. Repair
  455. Litchfield, Conn. - St. Michael's
  456. Wash. D. C. - Cathedral Jefferson lancet
  457. Pawtucket, R. I. - Trinity Ch., Nativity
  458. Norfolk, VA - Frazier Hall, Naval Base, 3 entrance (Jewish)
  459. Beverly - St. Peter's (Dorcas)
  460. Lynn - Sacred Heart
  461. Boston - Greek Cathedral (480)
  461-A. Boston - Greek Cathedral (589)
  462. Pawtucket, R. I. - Trinity alterations
  463. Gardiner, Me. - Christ Ch., alterations
  464. Bullions-Jewel
  465. Boston-St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 14 win.
  466. Auburndale - Ch. of the Messiah, chancel
  467. Boston-S. Elizabeth's Hospital, 12 win.
  468. Norfolk, Va.-Our Lady of Victory Chape (3 narthex, 1 transom, 2 door panels. Utilize 4 discarded medallions and make into 2 sacistry win. and 2 choir win. re-install 3 win. now in place)
  469. Pascoag, R.I., Calvary Church
  470. Albany, N. Y., St. Andrew's
  471. Leominster, Pilgrim Congregational
  472. Norfolk, VA., Our Lady of Victory Chapel (revision of rose, 4 nave windows)
  473. Attleboro, All Saints
  474. Bookplate-Stokes
  475. Springfield-Hope Congregational
  476. Boston-Holy Cross Cathedral
  477. Waban-Union Church
  478. Worcester-All Saints
  479. Colorado Springs, CO, Grace Ch.
  480. Boston-Greek Cathedral (461, 589)
  481. Boston-Catholic Boys' Club
  482. Providence Museum (repair)
  483. Plymouth-St. Peter's (repair)
  484. Providence, R.I.-St. Martin's
  485. New York City-Mrs. Smith's panels
  486. Easthampton-St. Philip's Ch.
  487. Samples of glass (movie-Mrs. Taylor)
  488. New York-Calvary Church, 5 apse
  489. Washington Cathedral-Physician's window
  490. Worcester-Sacred Heart
  491. St. Paul, Minn.-House of Hope Ch. 7 chapel
  492. Boston-Boston Univ., Mt. Chcorua
  493. Milton-Milton Academy
  494. Newton-St. Paul's
  495. Holyoke-Mother House (see 554)
  496. Waban-Union Church
  497. Plymouth-St. Peter's
  498. Boston-Trinity Ch. repair
  499. Transparency-Bambino
  500. Greenwood-Catholic Church
  501. Plymouth-St. Peter's Church
  502. Greenwood-Union Church
  503. Waban-Union Ch., clerestory
  504. Albany, N.Y.-St. Peter's
  505. Boston-St. Clement's Church
  506. Bronxville, N.Y.-Christ Church
  507. Charlton City-St. Joseph's Church
  508. Transparency-Small Christ Child
  509. Waterbury, Conn.-Bunker Hill Cong. Ch.
  510. Winchester-Unitarian Church (3 chapel)
  511. Boston (Shaw)
  512. Boston (Swift)
  513. Montgomery, AL-St. John's (repair)
  514. New York-St. John the Divine (St. Col. Chap.)
  515. Ipswich-Ascension Memorial Church
  516. Washington, D.C.-Rock Creek Parish (Brent)
  517. St. Paul, MN-House of Hope, 2 narthex
  518. Dedham-Ch. of Good Shepherd, clerestory
  519. Granite Falls, MN, St. Paul's Luth. (cross)
  520. Jamaica Plain-Blessed Sacrament
  521. Briston, R.I.-Christ Church
  522. West Roxbury-Jewish Cemetery (inscription)
  523. Lonsdale, R. I.-Our Christ Church
  524. Newton Center-Our Lady's (repair)
  525. Manchester, NH-Grace Ch., 2 lancets
  526. Newton-Vachon, 4 lights
  527. Winchester-Congregational Ch., Sir Galahad
  528. Winchester-Unitarian, Red Cross windows cloister
  529. Central Falls, R.I.
  530. Worcester-All Saints, 2 Baptistry
  531. Boston-Kennedy Residence
  532. Newton-Our Lady's, 2 lights
  533. Brookline-Temple Israel, repair
  534. Boston-St. Anthony's Shrine
  535. Boston-St. Anthony's Shrine, 14 Stations
  536. Boston-St. Anthony's Shrine, 2 murals
  537. Colorado Springs, Grace Ch., 2 narthex
  538. Colorado Springs-Grace Ch., Ascension
  539. Brookline-Temple Israel, inscriptions
  540. Brookline-Temple Israel, repair
  541. New York-Calvary, 6 quatrefoils
  542. New York-Calvary, 4 single lancets
  543. New York-Calvary, 3 lancets
  544. Boston-St. Anthony Shrine, 10 doorlights
  545. Melrose-Trinity Church, 2 aisle
  546. Burlington, Vt.-Cath. Immac. Conception
  547. Greenwood-Union Church
  548A. Washington Cath.-Choir, Civilizations
  548B. Washington Cath.-Choir, Jacob
  549. Providence-St. Martin's, 3 aisle
  550. Watertown-Methodist, repair
  551. Dorchester-St. Mark's
  552. North Saugus-Union Church
  553. Worcester-All Saints, repair
  554. Holyoke-Mother House, 2 confessional
  555. Milton-Reed, repair doorlight
  556. St. Augustine, Fla-Trinity Ch., Vaill Mem. window
  557. Winchester-Unitarian, repair vents
  558. Mt. Desert, ME
  559. Providence-St. Martin's, west window
  560. St. Louis, MO-St. Michael's, 2 cleretory
  561. St. Louis, MO-St. Michael's, 3 aisle
  562. Colorado Springs-Grace Ch., Cruxifixion
  563. Providence-St. Martin's, 3 lancet chapel win.
  564. Providence-St. Paul's Ch., DeMaris window
  565. Norwalk, CO-St. Paul's Ch.
  566. Sprinfield-Trinity Ch., 10 windows
  567. St. Louis, MO-1st Congreg'l (Creation)
  568. West Roxbury-St. Theresa's, chancel
  569. West Roxbury-St. Theresa's, 12 aisle
  570. West Roxbury-St. Theresa's, transept
  571. Evanston, Ill.-1st Presbyterian
  572. Dorchester-St. Mary's Ch., 2 chancel
  573. West Roxbury-St. Theresa's, 5 chapel
  574. St, Paul, MN-House of Hope, War Memorial
  575. Newton Hlds-St. Paul's, Ch. St. John window, St. Matthew
  576. Lawrence-Central Methodist, Missionary win.
  577. Colorado Springs-Grace Ch., Parables
  578. Colorado Springs-Grace Ch., Miracles
  579. Newport, R.I.-St. George's Ch., Missionary
  580. Philadelphia, PA-St. Martin's, chancel
  581. New York, N.Y.-Calvary, St. Francis
  582. Cleveland, OH-Ch. Covenant
  583. Cambridge-Theological Sch., rose
  584. Bronxville, NY-Christ Ch., Epiphany
  585. Providence, RI-St. Martin's s. porch win.
  586A. Washington Cath.-Education; large Gemini
  586B. Washington Cath.-Law
  587. St. Louis, MO-1st Congreg'l, 4 prophets
  588. Newton Corner-Grace Episcopal-Christ Window
  589. Boston-Greek Cathedral, Good Shepherd
  590. Colorado Springs-Grace Ch., 6 library
  591. Colorado Springs-Pauline Chapel, 2 sanc.
  592. West Roxbury-St. Theresa's Chapel, altar
  593. New York-All Angel's, transept window
  594. Cambridge-episcopal Theo. Sch., 9 aisle
  595. Washington Cath-Book of Common Prayer
  596. Bronxville, NY-Christ Ch., Boy Christ in Temple
  597. Washington, DC-Rock Creek, Bishop Kemper
  598. Philadelphia, PA-St. Martin's, repair
  599. Newton Corner-Grace Ch., Old Testament repair
  600. Newton Corner-Grace Ch., Creation
  601. Colorado Springs-Pauline Chapel, rose
  602. Litchfield-St. Michael's clerestory
  603. Cambridge-St. Peter's, St. Anne Window
  604. Ipswich-Ascension mem. Ch. 2 rose
  605. Taunton-St. Thomas'-chapel window
  606. Manchester, NH-Grace Ch., rose window
  607. Bronxville, NY-Christ Ch., Jesse window, Missionary-3 lancet
  608. Boston Univ.-Sch. Theology, Apostles-3 lancet, 8 sgle lancets, emblem
  609. Boyd, Minn.-Redeemer Lutheran Ch., Cruxifixion
  610. Rubaiyat transparency-rose center
  611. Boston-Old South Ch, rear chapel window
  612. Bronxville, NY-Christ Ch., Miracles aisle
  613. Rockport, MA-St. Mary's Church
  614. Lakewood, OH-Buchanan coat-of-arms
  615. Portland, OR-Holy Name Church
  616. Boston, MA-Old South Church, side chapel win.
  617. Watertown, CO-Christ Church
  618. Millwood, VA-Christ Ch. 2 aisle Baptism Annunciation
  619. Melrose, MA-Altar win. Rev Smith's chapel
  620. Transparency-Madonna and Child
  621. Transparency-Madonna and Child
  622. Albion, MI-Chapel, Starr Commonwealth for Boys
  623. Buffalo, NY-Westminster Ch., 3 vestibule
  624. Peabody, MA-St. Paul's Ch. Madonna and Child
  625. Washington Cathedral-Suter Memorial windows
  626. Millwood, VA-Christ Church, altar window
  627. Millwood, VA-Christ Ch. 2 aisle, emblems, designed only
  628. Bronxville, NY-Christ Ch., Ascension
  629. Taunton-1st Parish Ch., aisle
  630. Proctor, Vt.-Union Ch., 5 lancet rear window
  631. Chestnut Hill, Mass.-Ch. Redeemer, Epiphany window
  632. Plainfield, NJ-Crescent Avenue, Presbyterian Church
  633. Cleveland, OH-Our Lady of Peace Ch.
  634. Charlotte, NC-Myers Park Baptist Ch.
  635. Holyoke-Greylock Rest, Good Shepherd Medallion
  636. Providence, RI-Bishop Perry Mem. Win.
  637. Waban-Union Ch., 8 clerestory
  638. Orange, NJ-Grace Ch., "Baptistry win."
  639. Brookline-temple Ohabei Shalom
  640. Richmaond, VA-St. Paul's Church
  641. Cleveland, OH-St. Philip and St. James' Ch., 13 emblems
  642. Chestnut Hill-Ch. Redeemer, Te Deum win.
  643. Gates Mills, OH-Gilmour Academy, 7 emblems
  644. Arlington, MA-Ch. of Our Saviour
  645. Lawrence, MA-Grace Episcopal
  646. Newton Centre-First Parish Church, 3 2-lancet chapel windows
  647. Wollaston-St. Chrysostom's, chancel window
  648. Charlotte, NC-First Presbyterian, 10 chapel windows
  649. Cleveland, OH-St. Jerome's Church
  650. Attleboro-2nd Congregational Church, Mary and Martha lancet
  651. Chestnut Hill-Ch. Redeemer, 2-lancet windows angels
  652. Albany, NY-Westminster Presbyterian Ch., Antemann aisle window
  653. Charlotte, NC, 1st Presbyterian, Madonna
  654. Pittsfield-Congregational Ch.
  655. Chestnut Hill-First Church, 6 2-lancet win.
  656. Keene, NH-St. Jame's Ch., Nativity
  657. Morgantown, VA-Trinity Ch.
  658. Lynn-Ch. Incarnation, Mary Magdalene lancet
  659. Rockport-St. Mary's, 2 door lights
  660A. Washington Cathedral-Baptism
  660B. Washington Cathedral-Go ye into the world
  661. Charlotte, NC-Myers Park Baptist, Colonial lights
  662. Portland, OR-Holy Trinity, Iconastasis
  663. Winchester-Unitarian, 2 angel windows
  664. Akron, OH-Ch. Immac. Conception
  665. Washingon Cathedral-Sayre Memorial
  666. Rye, NY-Christ Ch. Chapel, 2 three-lancets
  667. Albion, MI-St. Geor and Dragon medallion
  668. North Andover-Merrimac College Fac. House
  669. St. Mary's City, Md.-Trinity Ch., 2 aisle
  670. Worcester-All Saints, St. Anthony window
  671. Wollaston, Methodist, chancel
  672. Durham, NC-Trinity Methodist
  673. Fairfield, CO-St. Paul's Ch.
  674. Colorado Springs, CO-Grace Ch., triptych
  675. Wakefield-Emmanuel, 2 aisle, A-St. Elizabeth; B-Madonna
  676. Parma, O.-Alvernai Rest Home, 10 chapel
  677. Gloucester-St. John's Church
  678. Worcester-Trinity Lutheran, 2 chapel
  679. Canton, OH-1st Presby. A-Chapel, B-Sanctuary
  680. Malden-St. Paul's, aisle
  681. West Roxbury-Jewish Benevolent Cemetery Assn.
  682. Franfort, KY-Ch. Ascension
  683. New Orleans, LA-Christ Ch. Cathedral, Nativity
  684. St. Louis, MO-1st Cong., chancel window
  685. Lewes, DE-St. Peter's, A-Baptism, B-Holy Communion, C-Tower, Virgin and Child
  686. Beverly-St. Peter's Church, 8 aisle
  687. Washington Cathedral-Lee and Jackson windows
  688. Wakefield-Emmanuel Ch., St. George, Rose window
  689. Wilmington, DE-Trinity Ch., 5 chapel
  690. Eaton Rapids, MI-VFW Home, Chapel Windows, Colorado State seal medallion for cottage
  691. Deham-St. Paul's Ch., St. George Window
  692. Braintree-Library, 5 windows
  693. Norfolk, VA.-Holy Trinity
  694. Melrose-Rev. Smith's private chapel, 5 windows
  695. Baltimore, MD.-Ch. Holy Nativity
  696. Chevy Chase, MD-Methodist Church
  697. Melrose-Congregational Church, 4 windows
  698. Dedham-Ch. Good Shepherd, chapel window (Flight into Egypt, Nativity)
  699. Cambridge-St. Peter's Ch., Ascension
  700. Portland, OR-St. Mary Magdalene Ch.
  701. West Columbia, TX-St. Mary's, rose
  702. Cranston, RI-Bethany Lutheran, chancel and rose
  703. Chappaqua, NY-Ch. St. Mary the Virgin, Rose
  704. Alexandria, VA-Westminster Presby., Rose
  705. Woodfords, ME.-(Irving and Casson) Trinity Church
  706. Albany, NY-Westminster Presby. (Welles Mem.)
  707. Wellesley-St. Andrew's Church
  708. Cambridge, St. Mary's Church
  709. Washington, GA-Ch. Mediator
  710. Washington Cathedral-Rose and 6 lancets (1/2)
  711. Grand Rapids, MI-South Congr. Church
  712. Worcester-Central Congr. Church
  713. Providence, RI-St. Martin's; St. Francis door panels
  714. Belmont-All Saints Church
  715. San Rafael, Calif.-St. Paul's Ch. 2 aisle, Mary and Martha; Christ Blessing Children
  716. Southampton, NY-St. Andrew's Church
  717. Washington, DC-St. David's Church, chancel
  718. Washington Cathedral-Worcester, John Elliot lancet
  719. Brighton-Temple Bnai Moshe
  720. Spartanburg, SC-Ch. Advent
  721. Holyoke-St. Paul's Church
  722. Worcester-State Mutual Insurance Co.
  723. Hartford, CT-Emanuel Evangel. Lutheran Church
  724. Worcester-All Saints Ch, 3 Chapel
  725. Albion, MI-Museum, Starr Commonwealth
  726. Brookline-All Saints Church
  727. Webster Groves, MO-Webster Hills Meth. Church
  728. Newton-Newton Centre Methodist Ch, chancel
  729. Bloomfield Hills, MI-Kirk-in-the-Hills
  730. Dover, NH-St. Thomas' Church
  731. Princeton, NH-Trinity Church